focusonstyle.com 2001-04-08

# Sharon Haver's Focus On Style Privacy Policy

**Sharon Haver's FOCUS ON STYLE    
PRIVACY POLICY**

Like most web businesses, Sharon Haver's Focus On Style captures both personal and aggregated information about visitors to our site. We explain here why we need that information and what we do (and won't do) with it.

Overview: We never disclose or sell personal information about you to third parties without your permission, unless compelled to do so by law. We store personal information on secure web servers, and you can review and change the personal information we keep about you.

**I. Why we retain and use information about our visitors**

Sharon Haver's Focus On Style collects personal and aggregate (anonymous) information about our site visitors for the following reasons:

A. To allow us to respond to your questions and comments: Since our web site revolves a great deal around being interactive with our visitors, we need to know who our visitors are so as to better respond to he questions submitted by those individual visitors.  
B. To know our audience: We use aggregated (anonymous) information about our visitors to understand our audience and to describe that audience to business partners, sponsors, and advertisers, which will enable us to provided an enhanced surfing experience for our visitors.   
C. For user convenience and customization: To allow us to customize the use of the site, to present the issues most important to our visitors in the fashion, style, and beauty worlds.   
D. For product improvements: To help us understand how visitors use our site and how we can improve it.  
E. To provide a better shopping environment: By knowing about our visitors it is possible for us to be able to offer those items and site links, that we feel our visitors most want to have, reducing the amount of time spent searching online.

**II. Types of information we collect**

Depending on how you use our site, Sharon Haver's Focus On Style may collect the following kinds of information:

A. Your name, and e-mail address, when you register for the site or e-mail us a question.   
B. Your user preferences, your interest in receiving our newsletters and product announcements, and similar information, which you can change at any time.  
C. Your credit-card number and mailing address, if you purchase one of the products offered by us exclusively. Any purchases made through our affiliates are subject to their privacy policy.  
D. Additional Personal information: If you subscribe to our newsletter we may collect personal information that allows us to target visitors with information, products or services which fits the visitor's specific needs or desires.  
E. Demographic information that you choose to provide, such as your gender, age, martial status, occupation, income, number and ages of your children, hobbies, zip code, mailing address, and so on. 

F. Aggregated usage data, such as the popularity of various pages on our site, the times of day when most site visits occur, and so on.

Personal information is stored on secure web servers, and is available on the site for you to review or modify at all times.

**III. Do we use cookies ?**

Yes, like other web sites, Sharon Haver's Focus On Style uses the technology called "cookies" to place small, anonymous data files on your computer. Depending on the version of Sharon Haver's Focus On Style you use, cookies may be used for the following purposes:  
A. To help us track the number of visitors and the popularity of our pages.  
B. To allow you to store personal preferences, such as your list of sites or list of purchases made.  
C. To give you the convenience of having your username submitted automatically once you've registered.

You can turn cookies off if you wish (see your browser's Help instructions). But Sharon Haver's Focus On Style features that rely on them will be disabled.

**IV. Sharon Haver's Focus On Style uses personal information about you in the following ways:**

A. To interact with you about problems or questions you may want answered  
B. To announce new Sharon Haver's Focus On Style products and enhancements  
C. To meet legal demands on us by certain administrative or legal organizations, if required to turn over such information.  
D. If you send email to us to respond to you with specific information if requested by you  
E. All reader letters are answered with an alias, or ghost phrase, and city rather than your real name.

**V. Sharon Haver's Focus On Style uses aggregate (anonymous) information about you in the following ways:**

A. To help us understand our audience as we grow our business.  
B. To promote ourselves to potential sponsors, advertisers or business partners

**VI. Sale or transfer of personal information retained by us.**

Sharon Haver's Focus On Style will never disclose or sell personal information about you, including your e-mail address, to any third party without your permission, unless compelled to do so by law.

**VII. Conclusion**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Nevertheless, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Finally, Sharon Haver's Focus On Style partners and third party Internet sites have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Sharon Haver's Focus On Style has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Sharon Haver's Focus On Style as outlined in this privacy policy. We have a right to change this policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If we decide for any reason to sell such information you will be given a right to opt out of such transfer. Any such procedure shall be outlined to you in our update.

**VIII. GENERAL DISCLAIMER  
**  
The materials in this site and any third-party sites are provided "as is" and without warranties of any kind, either express or implied. Sharon Haver's Focus On Style disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. Sharon Haver's Focus On Style does not warrant that the materials will be accurate, reliable or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that this site, or the server that makes it available, are free of viruses or other harmful components. Sharon Haver's Focus On Style does not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials in this site or in linked sites in terms of their correctness, accuracy, timeliness, reliability, or otherwise.   
The material that you read in this site is provided solely for entertainment, promotional, and commerce purposes. 

Sharon Haver's Focus On Style welcomes your questions and comments about privacy.

Our postal address is:  
P.O. Box 623  
Madison Square Station  
New York, NY 10159

Question and comments can be sent to the following address: [ suggestionbox@focusonstyle.com](mailto:privacypolicysuggestionbox@focusonstyle.com)

Policy updated 11/20/00.
